(this.webpackJsonpreactniceresume=this.webpackJsonpreactniceresume||[]).push([[0],{103:function(e,t,n){"use strict";n.r(t);var a=n(0),s=n(10),o=n.n(s),r=(n(75),n(40)),i=n(48),c=n(16),h=n(19),p=n(36),l=n(24),u=n(21),d=n(49),y=n(59),m=n.n(y),b=(n(78),n(79),n(26)),j=n.n(b),f=n(3),w=function(e){Object(l.a)(n,e);var t=Object(u.a)(n);function n(){return Object(c.a)(this,n),t.apply(this,arguments)}return Object(h.a)(n,[{key:"render",value:function(){if(!this.props.data)return null;var e=this.props.data.brand_name,t=this.props.data.description;return Object(f.jsxs)("header",{id:"home",children:[Object(f.jsxs)("nav",{id:"nav-wrap",children:[Object(f.jsx)("a",{className:"mobile-btn",href:"#nav-wrap",title:"Show navigation",children:"Show navigation"}),Object(f.jsx)("a",{className:"mobile-btn",href:"#home",title:"Hide navigation",children:"Hide navigation"}),Object(f.jsxs)("ul",{id:"nav",className:"nav",children:[Object(f.jsx)("li",{className:"current",children:Object(f.jsx)("a",{style:{fontSize:"14px"},className:"smoothscroll",href:"#home",children:"Home"})}),Object(f.jsx)("li",{children:Object(f.jsx)("a",{style:{fontSize:"14px"},className:"smoothscroll",href:"#about",children:"About"})}),Object(f.jsx)("li",{children:Object(f.jsx)("a",{style:{fontSize:"14px"},className:"smoothscroll",href:"#quiz",children:"Inquire"})})]})]}),Object(f.jsx)("div",{className:"row banner",children:Object(f.jsxs)("div",{className:"banner-text",children:[Object(f.jsx)(j.a,{bottom:!0,children:Object(f.jsx)("h1",{style:{color:"#ECAE00",paddingTop:"125px"},className:"responsive-headline",children:e})}),Object(f.jsx)(j.a,{bottom:!0,duration:1200,children:Object(f.jsxs)("h3",{style:{color:"#ECAE00"},children:[t,"."]})}),Object(f.jsx)("hr",{}),Object(f.jsx)(j.a,{bottom:!0,duration:2e3,children:Object(f.jsx)("ul",{className:"social",children:Object(f.jsxs)("a",{href:"#quiz",className:"smoothscroll button btn project-btn",children:[Object(f.jsx)("i",{className:"fa fa-book"}),"Get Started"]})})})]})}),Object(f.jsx)("p",{className:"scrolldown",children:Object(f.jsx)("a",{className:"smoothscroll",href:"#about",children:Object(f.jsx)("i",{className:"icon-down-circle"})})})]})}}]),n}(a.Component),O=function(e){Object(l.a)(n,e);var t=Object(u.a)(n);function n(){return Object(c.a)(this,n),t.apply(this,arguments)}return Object(h.a)(n,[{key:"render",value:function(){if(!this.props.data)return null;var e=this.props.data.social.map((function(e){return Object(f.jsx)("li",{children:Object(f.jsx)("a",{href:e.url,children:Object(f.jsx)("i",{className:e.className})})},e.name)}));return Object(f.jsx)("footer",{children:Object(f.jsxs)("div",{className:"row",children:[Object(f.jsx)(j.a,{bottom:!0,children:Object(f.jsxs)("div",{className:"twelve columns",children:[Object(f.jsx)("ul",{className:"social-links",children:e}),Object(f.jsxs)("ul",{className:"copyright",children:[Object(f.jsx)("a",{children:"\xa9 Copyright 2021 David Halliday"}),Object(f.jsx)("li",{children:Object(f.jsx)("a",{title:"Samson & Kashton Inc.",children:"Created by Samson & Kashton Inc."})})]})]})}),Object(f.jsx)("div",{id:"go-top",children:Object(f.jsx)("a",{className:"smoothscroll",title:"Back to Top",href:"#home",children:Object(f.jsx)("i",{className:"icon-up-open"})})})]})})}}]),n}(a.Component),g=function(e){Object(l.a)(n,e);var t=Object(u.a)(n);function n(){return Object(c.a)(this,n),t.apply(this,arguments)}return Object(h.a)(n,[{key:"render",value:function(){if(!this.props.data)return null;var e=this.props.data.name,t="images/"+this.props.data.image,n=this.props.data.bio,a=this.props.data.phone,s=this.props.data.email;return Object(f.jsx)("section",{id:"about",children:Object(f.jsx)(j.a,{duration:1e3,children:Object(f.jsxs)("div",{className:"row",children:[Object(f.jsx)("div",{className:"three columns",children:Object(f.jsx)("img",{className:"profile-pic",src:t,alt:"David Halliday Profile Pic"})}),Object(f.jsxs)("div",{className:"nine columns main-col",children:[Object(f.jsx)("h2",{style:{color:"#ECAE00"},children:"About Me"}),Object(f.jsx)("p",{children:n}),Object(f.jsx)("div",{className:"row",children:Object(f.jsxs)("div",{className:"columns contact-details",children:[Object(f.jsx)("h2",{style:{color:"#ECAE00"},children:"Contact Details"}),Object(f.jsxs)("p",{className:"address",children:[Object(f.jsx)("span",{children:e}),Object(f.jsx)("br",{}),Object(f.jsx)("span",{children:a}),Object(f.jsx)("br",{}),Object(f.jsx)("span",{children:s})]})]})})]})]})})})}}]),n}(a.Component),v=[{firstQuestion:[{question:"What type of vehicle are you looking for?",answers:[{type:"pathOne",content:"Car"},{type:"pathTwo",content:"Truck"},{type:"pathOne",content:"SUV"},{type:"pathThree",content:"New Hyundai"}]}],pathOne:[{question:"New or Used?",prev:"firstQuestion",answers:[{type:"pathOne",content:"New"},{type:"pathOne",content:"Used"}]},{question:"Gas or Hybrid/Electric?",prev:"pathOne",answers:[{type:"pathOneGasPath",content:"Gas"},{type:"pathOneHybrid",content:"Hybrid/Electric"}]}],pathOneGasPath:[{question:"Monthly Budget?",prev:"pathOne",hasInput:!0,inputContent:"Prefer to pay in cash?",answers:[{type:"pathOneGasPath",content:"Less than 200"},{type:"pathOneGasPath",content:"200-300"},{type:"pathOneGasPath",content:"300-400"},{type:"pathOneGasPath",content:"400-500"},{type:"pathOneGasPath",content:"500-600"},{type:"pathOneGasPath",content:"More than 600"}]},{question:"Are you trading in a vehicle?",prev:"pathOneGasPath",answers:[{type:"pathOneGasPath",content:"Yes"},{type:"pathOneGasPath",content:"No"}]},{question:"Choose one of the following:",prev:"pathOneGasPath",answers:[{type:"pathOneGasPath",content:"Import"},{type:"pathOneGasPath",content:"Domestic (North America)"},{type:"pathOneGasPath",content:"European"}]},{question:"What year were you looking for?",prev:"pathOneGasPath",answers:[{type:"pathOneGasPath",content:"2014-2015"},{type:"pathOneGasPath",content:"2016-2017"},{type:"pathOneGasPath",content:"2018-2019"},{type:"pathOneGasPath",content:"2020-2021+"}]},{question:"What mileage do you expect?",prev:"pathOneGasPath",answers:[{type:"pathOneGasPath",content:"0-20,000"},{type:"pathOneGasPath",content:"30,000-60,000"},{type:"pathOneGasPath",content:"70,000-100,000"},{type:"pathOneGasPath",content:"More than 100,000"}]},{question:"What features/packages are you looking for?",prev:"pathOneGasPath",hasInput:!0,inputContent:"Got a trim/model in mind?",answers:[{type:"pathOneGasPath",content:"Basic",packageOptions:["- Steel rims on hubcaps or plain alloy wheels","- Cloth seats","- Potential heated seats","- Basic safety features","- Basic driving assist features","- Back up camera","- Standard turn key","- Entry level infotainment system","- Manual seating adjustment","- Entry level engine and performance ability"]},{type:"pathOneGasPath",content:"Middle",packageOptions:["- Alloy wheels","- Cloth/leather seats","- Heated seats and steering wheel","- Blindspot, parking sensors, collision warnings","- Updated infotainment system (Apple Carplay/Android Auto)","- Potential sunroof","- Backup camera","- Potential driver-side power seat","- Entry level engine and performance ability"]},{type:"pathOneGasPath",content:"Loaded",packageOptions:["- Upgraded interior and exterior styling","- Leather seating","- Heated and cooled seats","- Advanced safety features","- Advanced driving assists","- Power liftgate and automatic trunk","- Built in navigation","- Upgraded sound and infotainment system","- Sunroof","- Power seats","- Turbo charged performance engine"]}]},{question:"When were you looking to purchase?",prev:"pathOneGasPath",answers:[{type:"pathOneGasPath",content:"Less than a week"},{type:"pathOneGasPath",content:"2 weeks"},{type:"pathOneGasPath",content:"1 month"},{type:"pathOneGasPath",content:"More than a month"}]},{question:"Please provide your contact information",prev:"pathOneGasPath",answers:[{type:"Done",content:"Name, Phone Number, Email, etc."}]}],pathOneHybrid:[{question:"Which type are you looking for?",prev:"pathOne",answers:[{type:"pathOneHybrid",content:"Hybrid"},{type:"pathOneHybrid",content:"Plug in Hybrid"},{type:"pathOneHybrid",content:"Electric"}]},{question:"Choose one of the following:",prev:"pathOneHybrid",answers:[{type:"pathOneHybrid",content:"Import"},{type:"pathOneHybrid",content:"Domestic (North America)"},{type:"pathOneHybrid",content:"European"}]},{question:"Monthly Budget?",prev:"pathOneHybrid",hasInput:!0,inputContent:"Prefer to pay in cash?",answers:[{type:"pathOneHybrid",content:"Less than 200"},{type:"pathOneHybrid",content:"200-300"},{type:"pathOneHybrid",content:"300-400"},{type:"pathOneHybrid",content:"400-500"},{type:"pathOneHybrid",content:"500-600"},{type:"pathOneHybrid",content:"More than 600"}]},{question:"Are you trading in a vehicle?",prev:"pathOneHybrid",answers:[{type:"pathOneHybrid",content:"Yes"},{type:"pathOneHybrid",content:"No"}]},{question:"What year were you looking for?",prev:"pathOneHybrid",answers:[{type:"pathOneHybrid",content:"2014-2015"},{type:"pathOneHybrid",content:"2016-2017"},{type:"pathOneHybrid",content:"2018-2019"},{type:"pathOneHybrid",content:"2020-2021+"}]},{question:"What mileage do you expect?",prev:"pathOneHybrid",answers:[{type:"pathOneHybrid",content:"0-20,000"},{type:"pathOneHybrid",content:"30,000-60,000"},{type:"pathOneHybrid",content:"70,000-100,000"},{type:"pathOneHybrid",content:"More than 100,000"}]},{question:"What features/packages are you looking for?",prev:"pathOneHybrid",hasInput:!0,inputContent:"Got a trim/model in mind?",answers:[{type:"pathOneHybrid",content:"Basic",packageOptions:["- Steel rims on hubcaps or plain alloy wheels","- Cloth seats","- Potential heated seats","- Basic safety features","- Basic driving assist features","- Back up camera","- Standard turn key","- Entry level infotainment system","- Manual seating adjustment","- Entry level engine and performance ability"]},{type:"pathOneHybrid",content:"Middle",packageOptions:["- Alloy wheels","- Cloth/leather seats","- Heated seats and steering wheel","- Blindspot, parking sensors, collision warnings","- Updated infotainment system (Apple Carplay/Android Auto)","- Potential sunroof","- Backup camera","- Potential driver-side power seat","- Entry level engine and performance ability"]},{type:"pathOneHybrid",content:"Loaded",packageOptions:["- Upgraded interior and exterior styling","- Leather seating","- Heated and cooled seats","- Advanced safety features","- Advanced driving assists","- Power liftgate and automatic trunk","- Built in navigation","- Upgraded sound and infotainment system","- Sunroof","- Power seats","- Turbo charged performance engine"]}]},{question:"When were you looking to purchase?",prev:"pathOneHybrid",answers:[{type:"pathOneHybrid",content:"Less than a week"},{type:"pathOneHybrid",content:"2 weeks"},{type:"pathOneHybrid",content:"1 month"},{type:"pathOneHybrid",content:"More than a month"}]},{question:"Please provide your contact information",prev:"pathOneHybrid",answers:[{type:"Done",content:"Name"}]}],pathTwo:[{question:"New or Used?",prev:"firstQuestion",answers:[{type:"pathTwo",content:"New"},{type:"pathTwo",content:"Used"}]},{question:"Monthly Budget?",prev:"pathTwo",hasInput:!0,inputContent:"Prefer to pay in cash?",answers:[{type:"pathTwo",content:"350-450"},{type:"pathTwo",content:"500-550"},{type:"pathTwo",content:"600-700"},{type:"pathTwo",content:"800-1000+"}]},{question:"Are you trading in a vehicle?",prev:"pathTwo",answers:[{type:"pathTwo",content:"Yes"},{type:"pathTwo",content:"No"}]},{question:"What size of Truck are you looking for?",prev:"pathTwo",hasInput:!0,inputContent:"Got another idea? Describe it below",answers:[{type:"pathTwo",content:"Mid size"},{type:"pathTwo",content:"Full size"}]},{question:"What year were you looking for?",prev:"pathTwo",answers:[{type:"pathTwo",content:"2014-2015"},{type:"pathTwo",content:"2016-2017"},{type:"pathTwo",content:"2018-2019"},{type:"pathTwo",content:"2020-2021+"}]},{question:"What mileage do you expect?",prev:"pathTwo",answers:[{type:"pathTwo",content:"0-20,000"},{type:"pathTwo",content:"30,000-60,000"},{type:"pathTwo",content:"70,000-100,000"},{type:"pathTwo",content:"More than 100,000"}]},{question:"What features and packages are you looking for? (select all that applies)",prev:"pathTwo",hasInput:!0,inputContent:"Got a trim/model in mind?",answers:[{type:"pathTwo",content:"Basic"},{type:"pathTwo",content:"Middle"},{type:"pathTwo",content:"Loaded"},{type:"pathTwo",content:"Two door"},{type:"pathTwo",content:"Quad cab"},{type:"pathTwo",content:"Crew cab"},{type:"pathTwo",content:"Short box"},{type:"pathTwo",content:"Regular box"},{type:"pathTwo",content:"Extended box"}]},{question:"When were you looking to purchase?",prev:"pathTwo",answers:[{type:"pathTwo",content:"Less than a week"},{type:"pathTwo",content:"2 weeks"},{type:"pathTwo",content:"1 month"},{type:"pathTwo",content:"More than a month"}]},{question:"Please provide your contact information",prev:"pathTwo",answers:[{type:"Done",content:"Name"}]}],pathThree:[{question:"Which type were you looking for?",prev:"firstQuestion",answers:[{type:"pathThreeCar",content:"Car"},{type:"pathThreeSUV",content:"SUV"}]}],pathThreeCar:[{question:"Which model are you interted in?",prev:"pathThree",answers:[{type:"pathThreeCar",content:"Elantra"},{type:"pathThreeCar",content:"Veloster"}]},{question:"Monthly Budget?",prev:"pathThreeCar",hasInput:!0,inputContent:"Prefer to pay in cash?",answers:[{type:"pathThreeCar",content:"Less than 200"},{type:"pathThreeCar",content:"200-300"},{type:"pathThreeCar",content:"300-400"},{type:"pathThreeCar",content:"400-500"},{type:"pathThreeCar",content:"500-600"},{type:"pathThreeCar",content:"More than 600"}]},{question:"Are you trading in a vehicle?",prev:"pathThreeCar",answers:[{type:"pathThreeCar",content:"Yes"},{type:"pathThreeCar",content:"No"}]},{question:"What features/packages are you looking for?",prev:"pathThreeCar",hasInput:!0,inputContent:"Got a trim/model in mind?",answers:[{type:"pathThreeCar",content:"Basic",packageOptions:["- Steel rims on hubcaps or plain alloy wheels","- Cloth seats","- Potential heated seats","- Basic safety features","- Basic driving assist features","- Back up camera","- Standard turn key","- Entry level infotainment system","- Manual seating adjustment","- Entry level engine and performance ability"]},{type:"pathThreeCar",content:"Middle",packageOptions:["- Alloy wheels","- Cloth/leather seats","- Heated seats and steering wheel","- Blindspot, parking sensors, collision warnings","- Updated infotainment system (Apple Carplay/Android Auto)","- Potential sunroof","- Backup camera","- Potential driver-side power seat","- Entry level engine and performance ability"]},{type:"pathThreeCar",content:"Loaded",packageOptions:["- Upgraded interior and exterior styling","- Leather seating","- Heated and cooled seats","- Advanced safety features","- Advanced driving assists","- Power liftgate and automatic trunk","- Built in navigation","- Upgraded sound and infotainment system","- Sunroof","- Power seats","- Turbo charged performance engine"]}]},{question:"When were you looking to purchase?",prev:"pathThreeCar",answers:[{type:"pathThreeCar",content:"Less than a week"},{type:"pathThreeCar",content:"2 weeks"},{type:"pathThreeCar",content:"1 month"},{type:"pathThreeCar",content:"More than a month"}]},{question:"Please provide your contact information",prev:"pathThreeCar",answers:[{type:"Done",content:"Name"}]}],pathThreeSUV:[{question:"Which model are you interested in?",prev:"pathThree",answers:[{type:"pathThreeSUV",content:"Venue"},{type:"pathThreeSUV",content:"Kona"},{type:"pathThreeSUV",content:"Tucson"},{type:"pathThreeSUV",content:"Santa Fe"},{type:"pathThreeSUV",content:"Palisade"}]},{question:"Monthly Budget?",prev:"pathThreeSUV",hasInput:!0,inputContent:"Prefer to pay in cash?",answers:[{type:"pathThreeSUV",content:"Less than 200"},{type:"pathThreeSUV",content:"200-300"},{type:"pathThreeSUV",content:"300-400"},{type:"pathThreeSUV",content:"400-500"},{type:"pathThreeSUV",content:"500-600"},{type:"pathThreeSUV",content:"More than 600"}]},{question:"Are you trading in a vehicle?",prev:"pathThreeSUV",answers:[{type:"pathThreeSUV",content:"Yes"},{type:"pathThreeSUV",content:"No"}]},{question:"What features/packages are you looking for?",prev:"pathThreeSUV",hasInput:!0,inputContent:"Got a trim/model in mind?",answers:[{type:"pathThreeSUV",content:"Basic",packageOptions:["- Steel rims on hubcaps or plain alloy wheels","- Cloth seats","- Potential heated seats","- Basic safety features","- Basic driving assist features","- Back up camera","- Standard turn key","- Entry level infotainment system","- Manual seating adjustment","- Entry level engine and performance ability"]},{type:"pathThreeSUV",content:"Middle",packageOptions:["- Alloy wheels","- Cloth/leather seats","- Heated seats and steering wheel","- Blindspot, parking sensors, collision warnings","- Updated infotainment system (Apple Carplay/Android Auto)","- Potential sunroof","- Backup camera","- Potential driver-side power seat","- Entry level engine and performance ability"]},{type:"pathThreeSUV",content:"Loaded",packageOptions:["- Upgraded interior and exterior styling","- Leather seating","- Heated and cooled seats","- Advanced safety features","- Advanced driving assists","- Power liftgate and automatic trunk","- Built in navigation","- Upgraded sound and infotainment system","- Sunroof","- Power seats","- Turbo charged performance engine"]}]},{question:"When were you looking to purchase?",prev:"pathThreeSUV",answers:[{type:"pathThreeSUV",content:"Less than a week"},{type:"pathThreeSUV",content:"2 weeks"},{type:"pathThreeSUV",content:"1 month"},{type:"pathThreeSUV",content:"More than a month"}]},{question:"Please provide your contact information",prev:"pathThreeSUV",answers:[{type:"Done",content:"Name"}]}]}],x=n(41);var T=function(e){return Object(f.jsx)("h2",{className:"question",children:e.content})};var C=function(e){return Object(f.jsxs)("div",{className:"questionCount",children:["Question ",Object(f.jsx)("span",{children:e.counter})]})},k=n(140),P=n(135),S=n(139),A=n(141),q=n(144),N=n(143),H=n(104),B={size:{width:40,height:40},sizeIcon:{fontSize:500}};function G(e){return Object(f.jsx)("div",{children:e})}function U(e){e.preventDefault()}var I=function(e){switch(function(e){var t="default";return"What features/packages are you looking for?"===e.question?t="package":"What features and packages are you looking for? (select all that applies)"===e.question?t="truck":"Please provide your contact information"===e.question&&(t="userContact"),t}(e)){case"package":return Object(f.jsx)(P.a,{item:!0,xs:12,sm:12,md:12,lg:4,children:Object(f.jsxs)(S.a,{className:e.classes.image,style:{textTransform:"none"},onClick:function(){e.onAnswerSelected(e.question,e.answerContent,e.answerType)},children:[Object(f.jsx)(k.a,{id:"paper",style:{fontSize:28,color:"white",background:"#07080fdc"},children:e.answerContent}),Object(f.jsx)(k.a,{id:"paper",style:{fontSize:18,textAlign:"left"},children:e.answerPackageOptions.map(G)})]})});case"truck":return Object(f.jsx)(P.a,{item:!0,xs:4,style:{paddingLeft:"30px"},children:Object(f.jsx)(A.a,{control:Object(f.jsx)(q.a,{className:B.size,onChange:e.handleCheckboxes,value:e.answerContent,name:e.answerContent}),label:Object(f.jsx)(H.a,{style:{fontSize:20,color:"black"},children:e.answerContent})})});case"userContact":return Object(f.jsx)(P.a,{item:!0,xs:12,children:Object(f.jsxs)("div",{style:{display:"flex",justifyContent:"center",alignItems:"center",flexDirection:"column"},children:[Object(f.jsx)("form",{id:"input-box",noValidate:!0,autoComplete:"off",onSubmit:U,children:Object(f.jsx)(N.a,{onChange:function(t){e.onChangeName(t.target.value)},id:"outlined-basic",style:{textAlign:"left"},label:Object(f.jsx)(H.a,{id:"typography",children:"Your name"}),variant:"outlined",inputProps:{min:0,style:{textAlign:"left",paddingTop:30,fontSize:20}}})}),Object(f.jsx)("form",{id:"input-box",noValidate:!0,autoComplete:"off",onSubmit:U,children:Object(f.jsx)(N.a,{onChange:function(t){e.onChangePhone(t.target.value)},id:"outlined-basic",style:{textAlign:"left"},label:Object(f.jsx)(H.a,{id:"typography",children:"Your phone number"}),variant:"outlined",inputProps:{min:0,style:{textAlign:"left",paddingTop:30,fontSize:20}}})}),Object(f.jsx)("form",{id:"input-box",noValidate:!0,autoComplete:"off",onSubmit:U,children:Object(f.jsx)(N.a,{onChange:function(t){e.onChangeEmail(t.target.value)},id:"outlined-basic",style:{textAlign:"left"},label:Object(f.jsx)(H.a,{id:"typography",children:"Your email"}),variant:"outlined",inputProps:{min:0,style:{textAlign:"left",paddingTop:30,fontSize:20}}})})]})});case"default":return Object(f.jsx)(P.a,{item:!0,xs:6,children:Object(f.jsx)(S.a,{className:e.classes.image,style:{textTransform:"none"},onClick:function(){e.onAnswerSelected(e.question,e.answerContent,e.answerType)},children:Object(f.jsx)(k.a,{className:e.classes.paper,style:{fontSize:18},children:e.answerContent})})})}},E=n(142),V="Done",z="",D="",M="",W="",L=[],Q=Object(E.a)((function(e){return{root:{flexGrow:1},paper:{padding:e.spacing(2),textAlign:"center",color:e.palette.text.secondary},image:{width:"100%",height:"100%",maxWidth:"100%",maxHeight:"100%",justifyContent:"flex-start",flexDirection:"row",display:"inline-block"},previous:{padding:e.spacing(.75),width:"100%",height:"100%",maxWidth:"100%",maxHeight:"100%",backgroundColor:"#07080fdc",borderRadius:"18%",fontWeight:"700"},finish:{padding:e.spacing(.75),width:"100%",height:"100%",maxWidth:"100%",maxHeight:"100%",backgroundColor:"#07080fdc",borderRadius:"10%",fontWeight:"700"},h1:{textAlign:"center",marginTop:"20px"},inputBox:{"& > *":{marginTop:e.spacing(1),width:"auto"}}}}));var R=function(e){var t=Q();function n(n){return Object(f.jsx)(I,{answerContent:n.content,answerType:n.type,answerPackageOptions:n.packageOptions,answer:e.answer,questionId:e.questionId,question:e.question,onAnswerSelected:e.onAnswerSelected,handleTextFieldChange:e.handleTextFieldChange,onChangeName:a,onChangePhone:s,onChangeEmail:o,handleCheckboxes:r,classes:t},n.content)}function a(e){D=e}function s(e){M=e}function o(e){W=e}var r=function(e){var t,n;e.target.checked?L.push(e.target.value):(t=L,n=e.target.value,L=t.filter((function(e){return e!==n})))};function i(e){e.preventDefault()}function c(){var n;return e.hasInput&&(n=Object(f.jsxs)("div",{style:{display:"flex",alignItems:"center",flexDirection:"column",width:"auto"},children:[Object(f.jsx)("h1",{className:t.h1,style:{textTransform:"none",fontSize:23},children:e.inputContent}),Object(f.jsx)("form",{id:"input-box",className:"input-box",noValidate:!0,autoComplete:"off",onSubmit:i,children:Object(f.jsx)(N.a,{onChange:function(e){z=e.target.value},id:"outlined-basic",style:{textAlign:"left"},label:Object(f.jsx)(H.a,{id:"typography",children:"Enter your response here (then press next arrow)"}),variant:"outlined",inputProps:{min:0,style:{textAlign:"left",paddingTop:30,fontSize:20}}})})]})),n}function h(){var n;return e.questionId>1&&(n=Object(f.jsxs)(P.a,{container:!0,direction:"row",justifyContent:e.answerOptions[0].type===V?"space-around":"space-between",alignItems:"center",children:[Object(f.jsx)(P.a,{children:Object(f.jsx)(S.a,{style:{textTransform:"none"},onClick:e.onBackButtonClick,children:Object(f.jsx)(k.a,{className:t.previous,style:{fontSize:28,color:"white"},children:"\xa0\xa0\xa0\u2039\xa0\xa0\xa0"})})}),Object(f.jsx)(P.a,{}),p(),l()]})),n}function p(){var n;return e.hasInput&&(n=Object(f.jsx)(P.a,{children:Object(f.jsx)(S.a,{style:{textTransform:"none"},value:e.answerOptions[0].type,onClick:function(){if(""!==z)e.onAnswerSelected(e.question,z,e.answerOptions[0].type),z="";else if(0!==L.length){for(var t="",n=0;n<L.length;n++)t+=L[n]+"\n";e.onAnswerSelected(e.question,t,e.answerOptions[0].type),L=[]}},children:Object(f.jsx)(k.a,{className:t.previous,style:{fontSize:28,color:"white"},children:"\xa0\xa0\xa0\u203a\xa0\xa0\xa0"})})})),n}function l(){var n;return e.answerOptions[0].type===V&&(n=Object(f.jsx)(P.a,{children:Object(f.jsx)(S.a,{style:{textTransform:"none"},value:"Done",onClick:function(){""!==D&&""!==M&&""!==W&&(e.onAnswerSelected(e.question,{name:D,phone:M,email:W},e.answerOptions[0].type),D="",M="",W="")},children:Object(f.jsx)(k.a,{className:t.finish,style:{fontSize:28,color:"white"},children:"\xa0\xa0\xa0Finish\xa0\xa0\xa0"})})})),n}return Object(f.jsx)("section",{id:"quiz",children:Object(f.jsx)(x.CSSTransitionGroup,{className:"container",component:"div",transitionName:"fade",transitionEnterTimeout:800,transitionLeaveTimeout:500,transitionAppear:!0,transitionAppearTimeout:500,children:Object(f.jsxs)("div",{children:[Object(f.jsx)(C,{counter:e.questionId}),Object(f.jsx)(T,{content:e.question}),Object(f.jsxs)("div",{className:t.root,id:"What features/packages are you looking for?"===e.question?"div-grid":"",children:[Object(f.jsx)(P.a,{container:!0,direction:"row",justifyContent:"center",children:e.answerOptions.map(n)}),c(),h()]})]},e.questionId)})})};var F=function(e){return Object(f.jsx)("section",{id:"quiz",children:Object(f.jsx)(x.CSSTransitionGroup,{className:"container result",component:"div",transitionName:"fade",transitionEnterTimeout:800,transitionLeaveTimeout:500,transitionAppear:!0,transitionAppearTimeout:500,children:Object(f.jsx)("div",{children:"Thank you for inquiring. Your answers have been sent to my email and I will be contacting you as soon as I can."})})})},Y=n(61),_="Done",J=function(e){Object(l.a)(n,e);var t=Object(u.a)(n);function n(e){var a;return Object(c.a)(this,n),(a=t.call(this,e)).state={foo:"bar",resumeData:{},counter:0,currentQuestion:1,currentPath:"firstQuestion",prevPath:"firstQuestion",question:"",answerOptions:[],answer:"",answersCount:{},result:"",hasInput:!1,inputContent:"",userAnswers:[]},d.a.initialize("UA-110570651-1"),d.a.pageview(window.location.pathname),a.handleAnswerSelected=a.handleAnswerSelected.bind(Object(p.a)(a)),a.handleBackButtonClick=a.handleBackButtonClick.bind(Object(p.a)(a)),a}return Object(h.a)(n,[{key:"getResumeData",value:function(){m.a.ajax({url:"./resumeData.json",dataType:"json",cache:!1,success:function(e){this.setState({resumeData:e})}.bind(this),error:function(e,t,n){console.log(n),alert(n)}})}},{key:"componentDidMount",value:function(){this.getResumeData(),this.setState({question:v[0].firstQuestion[0].question,answerOptions:v[0].firstQuestion[0].answers})}},{key:"handleAnswerSelected",value:function(e,t,n){var a=this;this.state.userAnswers.push({question:e,answer:t}),n!==_?setTimeout((function(){return a.setNextQuestion(n)}),300):setTimeout((function(){return a.setResults(a.getResults())}),300)}},{key:"handleBackButtonClick",value:function(e){var t=this.state.counter,n=this.state.currentQuestion,a=this.state.currentPath,s=this.state.prevPath;this.state.userAnswers.pop(),a!==s?(t=v[0][s].length,a=s):t>1&&(t-=1),s=v[0][a][t-1].prev,this.setState({question:v[0][a][t-1].question,answerOptions:v[0][a][t-1].answers,answer:"",counter:t,currentQuestion:n-1,currentPath:a,prevPath:s,hasInput:void 0!==v[0][a][t-1].hasInput&&v[0][a][t-1].hasInput,inputContent:void 0===v[0][a][t-1].inputContent?"":v[0][a][t-1].inputContent,userAnswers:this.state.userAnswers}),console.log(this.state.userAnswers)}},{key:"setUserAnswer",value:function(e){this.setState((function(t,n){return{answersCount:Object(i.a)(Object(i.a)({},t.answersCount),{},Object(r.a)({},e,(t.answersCount[e]||0)+1)),answer:e}}))}},{key:"setNextQuestion",value:function(e){var t=this.state.counter,n=this.state.currentQuestion,a=this.state.currentPath,s=this.state.prevPath;a!==e&&(t=0,a=e),s=v[0][a][t].prev,this.setState({question:v[0][e][t].question,answerOptions:v[0][e][t].answers,answer:"",counter:t+1,currentQuestion:n+1,currentPath:a,prevPath:s,hasInput:void 0!==v[0][e][t].hasInput&&v[0][e][t].hasInput,inputContent:void 0===v[0][e][t].inputContent?"":v[0][e][t].inputContent})}},{key:"getResults",value:function(){var e=this.state.answersCount,t=Object.keys(e),n=t.map((function(t){return e[t]})),a=Math.max.apply(null,n);return t.filter((function(t){return e[t]===a}))}},{key:"formatEmail",value:function(){for(var e="",t=0;t<this.state.userAnswers.length-1;t++)e+=this.state.userAnswers[t].question+" \n\n"+this.state.userAnswers[t].answer+" ||  \n\n";return e+=this.state.userAnswers[this.state.userAnswers.length-1].question+" \n\n"+this.state.userAnswers[this.state.userAnswers.length-1].answer.name+" \n\n"+this.state.userAnswers[this.state.userAnswers.length-1].answer.phone+" \n\n"+this.state.userAnswers[this.state.userAnswers.length-1].answer.email}},{key:"setResults",value:function(e){Y.a.send("service_x9h4pih","template_zo59si8",{name:this.state.userAnswers[this.state.userAnswers.length-1].answer.name,message:this.formatEmail()},"user_lDkxPxLwNuQZiXpJo7sRD"),console.log(this.formatEmail()),this.setState({result:_})}},{key:"renderQuiz",value:function(){return Object(f.jsx)(R,{answer:this.state.answer,answerOptions:this.state.answerOptions,questionId:this.state.currentQuestion,question:this.state.question,onAnswerSelected:this.handleAnswerSelected,onBackButtonClick:this.handleBackButtonClick,hasInput:this.state.hasInput,inputContent:this.state.inputContent,currentQuestion:this.state.counter})}},{key:"renderResult",value:function(){return Object(f.jsx)(F,{quizResult:this.state.result})}},{key:"render",value:function(){return Object(f.jsxs)("div",{className:"App",children:[Object(f.jsx)(w,{data:this.state.resumeData.main}),Object(f.jsx)(g,{data:this.state.resumeData.main}),this.state.result?this.renderResult():this.renderQuiz(),Object(f.jsx)(O,{data:this.state.resumeData.main})]})}}]),n}(a.Component),K=function(e){e&&e instanceof Function&&n.e(3).then(n.bind(null,146)).then((function(t){var n=t.getCLS,a=t.getFID,s=t.getFCP,o=t.getLCP,r=t.getTTFB;n(e),a(e),s(e),o(e),r(e)}))};o.a.render(Object(f.jsx)(J,{}),document.getElementById("root")),K()},75:function(e,t,n){},78:function(e,t,n){}},[[103,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.a253175f.chunk.js.map